Narrator: 2
Verb phrases
Narrator: 1, B
F: Fashion has come full circle, and long skirts are now back, like in the 70s.
Narrator: 2, A
M: Our dog needs a ridiculous amount of food. He’s eating us out of house and home.
Narrator: 3, G
F: I could tell immediately that Jackie was upset. She wears her heart on her sleeve.
Narrator: 4, C
M: I thought it was best that I told Matt what I knew about his new girlfriend.
Sometimes you have to be cruel to be kind.
Narrator: 5, I
F: The boss is furious with you about yesterday’s meeting.
I think you should lie low this morning and keep out of his way.
Narrator: 6, F
M: A man turned up at the door pretending to be a policeman
and tried to convince my grandmother to give him her credit card details.
Luckily, I was there, and I sent him packing.
Narrator: 7, H
F: Telling a joke is a good way to break the ice at the start of a presentation.
Narrator: 8, D
M: I drank far too much coffee yesterday, and as a result I didn’t sleep a wink.
Narrator: 9, E
F: Nobody knows what happened to the missing walkers. They seem to have vanished into thin air.